<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Security Notes</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Security Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 22:10:36 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OSWE/AWAE Preparation</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/01/22/oswe/awae-preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 22:10:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/01/22/oswe/awae-preparation/</guid>
      <description>AWAE-Preparation This post contains all trainings and tutorials that could be useful for offensive security&amp;rsquo;s OSWE certification. I will be updating the post during my lab and preparation for the exam.
Course Syllabus: https://www.offensive-security.com/documentation/awae-syllabus.pdf
Before registering for AWAE:  Cross-Site Scripting:  XSS XMLHttpRequest Specification AtMail Email Server Appliance 6.4 - Persistent Cross-Site Scripting Persistent XSS Hijack Session using socat   XSS and MySQL  PentesterLab: XSS and MySQL FILE  https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microcorruption CTF - Tutorial</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/11/25/microcorruption-ctf---tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 22:10:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/11/25/microcorruption-ctf---tutorial/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this post I will share my learnings and research work done during microcorruption CTF challenge.
What is Microcorruption? It&amp;rsquo;s an embedded security CTF challenge where you are given a debugger and a device (a smart lock), you will be given different levels of challenges to unlock the device, find flgs, find code vulnerabilitys, memory corruption bugs etc.
You&amp;rsquo;ll use the debugger to reverse-engineer the code for each level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptography I - Stanford University - Week 1</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/11/24/cryptography-i---stanford-university---week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 16:52:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/11/24/cryptography-i---stanford-university---week-1/</guid>
      <description>Week 1. This week&amp;rsquo;s topic is an overview of what cryptography is about as well as our first example ciphers. You will learn about pseudo-randomness and how to use it for encryption. We will also look at a few basic definitions of secure encryption.
 History Discrete Probability  Birthday paradox  Stream Ciphers  Information theoretic security  Stream Ciphers PRG Attacks on OTP / stream ciphers Modern broken stream ciphers Better modern stream cipher Let’s do some Salsa!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptography I - Stanford University - Week 1</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/11/24/cryptography-i---stanford-university---week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 16:52:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/11/24/cryptography-i---stanford-university---week-1/</guid>
      <description>Week 2:
Crypto notes - Stanford - Week 2  Block Ciphers  Pseudo Random Function (PRF) Pseudo Random Permutation (PRP) Secure PRF PRF =&amp;gt; PRG  Data Encryption Standard  []() []()    Block Ciphers A block cipher maps n bits of inputs to n bits of output. Examples : - 3DES: n=64bits, k=168 bits - AES: n=128bits, k = 128,192,256 bits
Block ciphers are typically built by iteration with a round function R(k, m).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/11/11/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 14:59:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/11/11/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Welcome!
In this site I will be sharing my learning and experiences i gained during a pentest, a CTF, wargame or any security challenges, basically everything i learn or want to learn. Hoping to help someone in similar situations and get feedback from you!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>